Pine Hills Fortnightly Club; Records apap031
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Papers Presented, 1911-2003; 6; 0.78 cubic ft.
  - "Women in the Board Room: The Fallout from the Social Movements and the Economic Realities of the Present," by Anne Roberts, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 19)
  - "From The Abacus to the Internet: Computers and Their Implications," by Anne F. Roberts, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 20)
  - "Recollecting the Great Depression," by Charity Roth, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 21)
  - "Letchworth State Park," by Vera Scadura, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 22)
  - "Poets," by Dories Welish, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 23)
  - "Stamp Collecting," by Vera Scadura, 1999 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 24)
  - "The Isle of Man," by Eleanor Lattimer, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 25)
  - "Aleutian Islands," by Vera Scadura, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 26)
  - "Population Control in China: Where have all the flowers gone?" by Joan Taylor, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 27)
  - "Contemporary Chinese Music and Dance," by Eleanor Clarke, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 28)
  - "Profits and Problems: U.S., 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 29)
  - "Some Governors who Lived in the Mansion," by Anne Roberts, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 30)
  - "Cat, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 31)
  - Programs, 1999, 2002 (Box 3 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 32)
  - "North Carolina's Delegates to the Constitutional Convention," by Evelyn Jenkins, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 1)
  - "Alexander Hamilton, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 2)
  - "All Gaul is divided...", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 3)
  - "American Architecture", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 4)
  - "Author: Winifred Holtby", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 5)
  - "Background of the Constitution", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 6)
  - "Miracle at Philadelphia", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 7)
  - "Mormonism", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 8)
  - "New Hope For Iran", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 9)
  - "Novel: The Mother", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 10)
  - "Once Upon a Time, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 11)
  - "Opening Utopian Gates", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 12)
  - "Rhode Island Food", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 13)
  - "Poland", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 14)
  - "The Triangle Fire: It's (sic) Effect on Women's Working Conditions 1910, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 15)
  - "Washington Irving, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 16)
  - "Genealogy", Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 17)
  - "1920, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 18)
  - "Lindbergh Episode," by Alice Hastings Murphy, Undated (Box 4 (6-Papers Presented), Folder 19)